<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tien Nguyen</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tien Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introducton I will be analyzing figure skating data from the 2018 Winter Olympics. I will be looking at two datasets: performances and scores. The performances dataset contains performance ID, program name, name of the skater, the home country of the skater, the final place the skater finished, the order in which the skater skated, the total score for the program, the total score of all elements in the program, the total score of all components in the program, and the total deductions for the performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description>0. Introduction My project involves conducting statistical tests in Hass avocado sales between 2015-2018 to uncover any statistical significance among the variables in the dataset. This was done by analyzing relationships between these variables. The avocado dataset contains 18249 observations and 14 variables. The main numeric variables I looked at were average price of a single avocado, the total volume (number) of avocados sold, how many avocados sold were PLU 4046, PLU 4225, and PLU 4770, the total number of bags sold, the total number of small bags sold, the total number of large bags sold, and the total number of extra large bags sold.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
